[opening theme music playing]
[wind gusting]
GYEONGSEONG CREATURE 2
[melodic pop music playing]
[music stops]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[groans]
[panting]
[coughs]
[breathing heavily]
[unsettling music playing]
[breathing shakily]
[moaning in distance]
[boy] Please don't kill us.
[girl's muffled crying]
[boy] Don't kill us.
[Chae-ok breathing nervously]
[girl's crying continues]
Don't kill us. Don't kill us.
What happened in here?
Don't kill us.
Did I kill everyone?
[girl whimpers, sobs]
[Chae-ok gasps]
[unsettling music continues]
[chanting] Hurray for Independence!
Hurray for Independence!
- [cheering]
- [pensive music playing]
[Chae-ok] Gyeongseong will now…
welcome in a new spring.
[emotional music playing]
But my winter
has not yet ended.
I will be left behind alone in this hell.
Forgotten by everyone.
[music fades]
So why…
after all this time,
are these things happening all over again?
Master Jang.
[Chae-ok] How is it possible
that you are still here?
[sighs]
You, um,
must have me confused with someone else.
Who's Master Jang?
I have no idea who that person is.
Your name is not Jang Tae-sang?
No, sorry.
My name is Jang Ho-jae.
Are you all right?
[Chae-ok] What was I thinking?
There's no way it could be him.
[Ho-jae] Excuse me.
[Chae-ok] It's just not possible.
Answer me.
Wait a minute.
[wistful music playing]
You haven't answered me yet.
Answer what?
Well, for one, tell me your name.
What were you doing there that night,
and how are you connected to Oh Ki-hoon?
And why do I have to tell you any of that?
I don't know you.
Because I don't want to
take the fall for this.
The police believe I'm the murderer
all because I was at the wrong place
at the wrong time.
So tell me, what were you doing there?
I received a request
to find a missing person.
I was at the hotel
because I was looking for Oh Ki-hoon.
He was already murdered when I got there.
Looks like we're both
in the same boat, then.
No, we're not in the same boat.
You're the only one they've accused.
You know the police have footage of you.
So I think you'll be a suspect as well.
So what?
Wanna work together?
I mean, neither of us are guilty here,
and yet we're both considered
prime suspects,
so how about we just help one another out?
You ask as if
I'm going to say yes already.
There's no downside to working with me.
I'm not trying to sound
too full of myself saying this,
but I am actually quite well-known
for this type of work.
Well, I work on my own.
I don't like to carry deadweight.
You're not the only one
who likes working alone here.
But a guy was murdered, huh?
I won't let you punch me again.
Word of advice?
You won't be able to handle it
even if you do find the murderer.
Thanks for your concern,
but I'll be the judge of that.
Go for it, then.
Just stay away,
and don't ride on my coattails.
Ride on your coattails?
You really… think that?
Yes, I do.
Now leave me alone and solve your problems
on your own, all right?
[sighs]
♪ Candles lit ♪
♪ In the room ♪
♪ Staring for ♪
♪ Long time ♪
GYEONGSEONG CREATURE
BETWEEN FACT AND DISTORTION
EPISODE 2
SIGN
Oh, you're back.
So what happened out there?
Were you able to find the woman at all?
[Ho-jae] Not now.
I'm not really in the mood to talk.
Hey, do you know a guy named Master Jang?
Master who?
Master Jang.
Not at all. Never heard of him.
Why?
I found the woman,
and she called me that name.
What'd you say?
Well, I told her that I wasn't.
However, that name
sounded really familiar,
as if I've heard you use it before
or something.
Me? No way.
I've never heard the name until just now.
[Ho-jae chuckles]
[Yong-gil] I'm about to make some ramen.
Want some? It'll be quick.
Uh, no, I'm good.
[intriguing music playing]
[sighs]
[phone buzzing]
Hi, Bugang Company, Ho-jae speaking.
Who am I speaking with?
[music fades]
[unsettling music playing]
[mysterious music playing]
[phone buzzes]
[Madam Na] Job request.
Missing person's name, Jang Ho-jae.
In his early thirties.
He's been missing for about a year.
They don't have a photo.
Sending a drawing for now.
Are you available?
Hmm.
[unsettling music playing]
[siren wailing]
[tires squealing]
[Ho-jae] Here you go.
[woman] Thank you so much.
[music fades]
[slurps]
Oh. Ethiopian.
[Ho-jae] Paraguayan.
[chuckles]
I don't know coffee that well.
I took a wild guess.
I don't know it that well either.
I read the label just now.
Ah! [laughs]
So I'm gonna bet you're not here
to discuss my coffee collection.
So why don't we get to it?
Why did you come here?
In that case…
I'm here to show you this.
JONGNO-GU SERIAL MURDER
CASE REPORT
[pensive music playing]
A series of murders
have been occurring in our jurisdiction
for at least the past two months.
Mr. Oh Ki-hoon is the fifth victim.
The five cases appear to be
identical in every way.
Each of the bodies we've found so far
is missing an eye, as well as the brain.
The brain?
Like the one inside of here?
To be honest, none of our investigators
know what's going on here.
Nobody at the station has ever
seen this kind of murder before.
And we still haven't figured out
the murder weapon they used
to suck out the brain.
But wait, um,
so this was all done by one person?
Yes. It's the work of one killer.
[light jazz music playing]
Still no answer?
You're more than welcome to leave
your phone number with me instead.
If Silverbill accepts the job,
I'll text you.
Have you been working long
with this Silverbill?
I don't take questions
regarding Silverbill.
Only regarding missing persons.
[man] The job on Oh Ki-hoon…
are you the one who took it?
Ah!
So you're essentially
no more than a receptionist…
aren't you?
[door closes]
I'M HEADING OVER NOW
DON'T COME
[unsettling music playing]
[squelching]
I'm curious though. Why show this to me?
Why go out of your way to share
private records of your investigation?
I think it's only fair to you.
You should at least know what kind of case
you're getting involved in
and just how absolutely horrible
and gruesome the killer really is.
It was the very least I could do for you.
You're new to the Violent Crimes Unit.
I transferred two months ago.
How many cases have you solved?
Just a couple so far. That's it.
Yet you're in charge of
a serial murder case?
It's not like I get to pick
whatever case I want.
They tell me what to do, and I do it.
Is that why you're hiding
a recording device there?
[Ho-jae chuckles]
It's pretty obvious in that spot,
don't you think?
[sighs] Sorry about that.
It's quite all right.
Caught you off guard?
Yes. [chuckles]
[phones buzzing]
ANOTHER VICTIM FOUND
ALL DETECTIVES TO THE CRIME SCENE
There's been another murder.
That makes six dead.
- I'll go with you.
- What?
- [door opens]
- Hey!
[unsettling music playing]
[tires squealing]
[sirens wailing]
[officer 1] We ask for your cooperation.
Please back up.
Do not take pictures. Back up!
Back up, please.
- Watch out.
- This is a crime scene. Please back up.
- Do you know who was hurt?
- This is a crime scene.
- [man] Huh?
- Please move. Steer clear and away.
[unsettling music continues]
[camera shutter clicking]
[sighs]
[tuts] What a night.
[woman 1] I can't believe
this happened to her.
[woman 2] I know. My goodness.
What do we do?
[woman 1] How could this happen?
She was such a kind woman.
[phone buzzing]
MADAM NA
[music fades]
Who are you?
[man] How do you know Jang Ho-jae?
Did you kill Madam Na?
[mysterious music playing]
She wouldn't answer my questions
and kept beating around the bush.
And so…
[Chae-ok chuckles]
You bastard. I'll kill you.
Tell me where you are.
Tell me where you are right now.
You didn't answer my question.
How about you answer it first?
[officer 2] Please move out of the way.
Please move.
Everyone, please step back.
This is a crime scene.
Step back.
[officer 1] Step back, please.
Thanks for the ride.
We got here pretty quick.
[indistinct chattering]
[mysterious music playing]
[disconnect tone]
[unsettling music playing]
- [tires squeal]
- [car horn honks]
[breathing heavily]
[music fades]
[water burbling]
[breathing heavily]
[fluttering]
[unsettling music playing]
[thud echoing]
[dramatic music playing]
[Chae-ok gasps]
That's strange.
[music subsides]
Why aren't you dead yet?
From that impact,
your neck should be broken
and your intestines ruptured.
If you were human.
[loud thud]
[groans]
Tell me who you are.
Why'd you kill Madam Na?
Did you kill Oh Ki-hoon too?
Are you the one behind all of this?
[scoffs]
You're…
one of us, huh?
[suspenseful music playing]
[skin tearing]
[grunts]
[blood squelching]
[reverential music playing]
[grunts, groans]
You are.
[grunts]
What the fuck are you doing?
Hey, are you all right? Are you hurt?
Hello? Someone's been stabbed.
Please come quick. Hurry!
Are you okay? Hold on a little longer.
Help's on the way.
Stay with me, all right?
Hey. Hey! Hey, you have to stay awake.
Come on!
[muffled] You have to stay awake!
Please wake up!
- [echoing]
- [gasps]
[Tae-sang] Did you sleep okay?
[tender piano music playing]
Hmm.
You were sleeping so peacefully,
I didn't wanna wake you.
♪ Candles lit in the room… ♪
Oh, Master Jang.
[breathing shakily]
What's wrong?
Did you… have a bad dream or something?
♪ Staring for long time… ♪
Actually, it was worse than a bad dream.
♪ Where the wind came from… ♪
It was terrifying…
[sobs]
…and lonely.
Don't worry.
It was only a dream.
What matters is you're awake now.
[music continues]
Don't worry, okay?
I'm not gonna go anywhere.
I will be right here with you.
Right here by your side forever.
♪ Candles lit in the room ♪
♪ Wind from the chink, swayed by it ♪
♪ It's like my mind ♪
♪ It's just like me ♪
♪ Staring for long time ♪
[nurse 1] Please let go.
She's lost a lot of blood
and needs treatment immediately.
[music continues]
[music fades]
[phone buzzing]
Mr. Chairman. I'm on level one. Why?
What?
What about last night?
[footsteps approaching]
JAZZ BAR OWNER IN HER 40S MURDERED
BODY FOUND WITH DAMAGED EYE
I'll look into it and see what happened.
Mr. Chairman, pay it no attention.
I'm on it. Don't worry.
Okay?
[mysterious music playing]
[sighs] Call Seung-jo for me.
[Kuroko04] Yes, sir. Right away.
[unsettling music playing]
[keypad beeps]
Hey, where is the patient
that was in there?
I don't know, Doctor.
[sighs]
Doctor, will she be okay?
Do you know if there are any updates?
Uh, so actually, we're looking for her.
They've been searching the entire building
to see where she is…
[monitor beeping]
…but it seems like she has disappeared.
[Ho-jae] Disappeared?
Where would--
[unsettling music playing]
[sighs]
You didn't need to summon everyone
just for this.
Don't you think
you're overreacting a little--
[loud bang]
[breathing heavily]
You are not to cause any more trouble.
And stop going rogue.
It's because I went rogue
that Oh Ki-hoon was taken care of.
He figured us out.
Listen and keep your mouth shut
when I am talking.
[Seung-jo] How long
are we going to live like this?
Are you gonna have us
live in hiding forever?
With the powers we've got,
we should be living however we want to!
[shoe crunching]
[Seung-jo grunts]
If you can't control
your impulsive behavior,
then you have no real power.
You only bring chaos and violence
wherever you go, Seung-jo.
So from now on,
this is what's going to happen.
Stay hidden
until all the commotion dies down.
Keep quiet and behave.
I don't wanna hear a peep from you.
[unsettling music continues]
Mess up again, and you will be going
directly to the chairman
to explain why
you've disappointed him yet again.
I would be careful if I were you.
[breathing heavily]
[Seung-jo] Are you sure he's dead?
Ho-jae.
You were in charge of his execution.
Seung-jo, don't ever
bring that person's name up again,
or you're dead.
[loud bang]
JONGNO POLICE STATION
[groans]
Six victims and no suspects.
No fingerprints. No evidence.
And no patterns either.
None of the victims have any relation
except the way they were murdered.
[man 1 sighs]
[groans]
Were you able to get any leads, Detective?
Detective Noh.
Noh Ji-su!
You have any updates?
Oh, um… Well, nothing to report so far.
- That's all?
- Sorry?
Why are you sitting at your desk
doing nothing?
Shouldn't you be somewhere right now?
Like, um, following around Jang Ho-jae.
It's what I told you to do,
not listen to music at your desk.
I'll be off, Captain.
[sighs]
Why hasn't he come back yet?
[mysterious music playing]
[woman] The person they call Silverbill?
I don't know where she lives.
Madam Na probably didn't know much
about them either.
They communicated
almost everything by text.
It looked like they only called each other
if it was urgent.
Besides Madam Na, no one else knows
what the Silverbill looks like.
[music fades]
Why is it so bleak in here?
[woman] Goodness.
They say we are only given today
and never promised tomorrow.
I never thought she would go like that.
[woman gasps]
Uh… It's way too much. No.
I remember you said
your grandson graduated.
Go buy him some new clothes.
[chuckles]
He's just so smart.
He took a job exam recently,
and he passed the whole thing.
He passed the interview first time around.
Wow, he's got a job already?
He is going to work at Jeonseung Lab now!
[laughs]
I think I'll buy him a new suit.
That's what I'll do.
Thank you, President Jang.
I'm not the president. Yong-gil is.
Aw. All of us on the outside know
you're the real president, Master Jang.
It's your ideas.
What'd you say?
Huh?
[wistful music playing]
The name you just called me.
Who's Master Jang?
Oh, well…
where you work now,
there was a pawnshop there that was called
the House of Golden Treasure.
My mother said
he was a kind and good person.
In fact, everyone from that period
had good things to say about Master Jang.
Yes.
Right. So,
who was he?
He owned
the pawnshop.
Master Jang.
[wistful music continues]
[grunts]
[man 1] The results of Experiment A0-67,
Mr. Chairman.
Tell me, how far did we get this time?
We were not able to pass stage two again.
[unsettling music playing]
[loud thud echoing]
[low groaning]
[snarling]
[creature snarls]
It feeds off of your fear,
so don't be frightened.
And do your best to remain calm,
or else it will attack you.
[footsteps thudding]
[metallic clattering]
[snarls]
[snarling]
[growling ferociously]
[footsteps thudding]
[high-pitched snarling]
[growls]
Don't move. Keep very still.
[man whimpering]
[growls ferociously]
[screaming] What is that thing?
Keep calm, and don't break eye contact.
Get me outta here! Someone help!
- [skin tearing]
- [man screams]
- [bones crunching]
- [blood squelching]
[body thuds]
[snarling]
[unsettling music playing]
I really don't have
much more patience for your failures.
If you can't find a way
to control the test subjects,
then the experiment won't move forward.
If these results
continue to be insufficient, then I have
no other choice but to bring him back.
This project will not fail.
You received that Najin in your brain
as a gift from the last chairman
to serve as Jeonseung's protector.
He provided you
with an opportunity to do great things.
[pensive music playing]
Don't ever forget how easily
a replacement can be found for you.
So I wouldn't make any more mistakes
from here on out.
I have not forgotten.
- I will succeed soon.
- [groans]
[sighs]
And Seung-jo?
He won't cause any more trouble for us.
I made sure of it.
Tell him that if he messes up again,
then I will lock him up forever.
A string of murders?
I mean, in this day and age?
[sighs]
[unsettling music playing]
[music fades]
[Yong-gil slurps]
Why aren't you eating, hmm?
It's getting soggy. You're wasting it.
I heard this was a pawnshop
back in the day.
The House of Golden Treasure.
Oh yeah?
[Yong-gil slurps]
And the owner was a Master Jang.
[coughing]
[coughing continues]
Even one of our informants knew.
You really didn't know?
Not sure. [coughs]
I might've heard about it and just forgot.
So what?
Let me ask.
When I was in that accident last year,
well, is there anything else you left out?
No, there isn't.
I think I told you everything pretty much.
Why are you asking?
What else are you curious about?
It's just, what if there is
something important I forgot?
I can't even remember
who I was before.
Everything that I know
is from what you've told me.
Ho-jae, you trust me?
Of course.
And you know there's no one in the world
who cares about you more than I do, right?
[chuckles] Yes, I know.
So take my word for it.
I think you're much better off now
than you were before the accident.
And maybe not remembering everything
is really all for the best, you know?
When I look at you, I finally understand
why they say that ignorance is bliss.
Everything's been reset,
so I think you should just
take advantage of the opportunity, okay?
Was my life before that bad?
Ah! You're reading way too much into it.
That is not what I'm saying here.
Well, didn't you just say
that ignorance is bliss, Yong-gil?
So I can't help but wonder
if my life, well, wasn't, uh… very good.
Like, was I lousy?
You need to know there was an accident,
and you lost your memory.
I only want to remember…
who I was.
Ho-jae.
Please tell me.
What kind of guy was I?
Was I a screwup or what, huh?
[wistful music playing]
Huh?
All right, then.
Well, you were a total deadbeat,
and that's the truth.
You were either depressed,
miserable, or unhappy.
There was always something wrong.
For example, at times, you were paranoid,
and that would result in
you having tantrums.
You would throw things, destroy furniture,
and had bad anger management issues.
But now, you're doing much better,
so I don't want you to keep dwelling
on your past life anymore.
All you need to do
is be in this moment, have some faith,
explore, and enjoy your life, okay?
To begin, how about you eat
the bowl of jajangmyeon.
I cooked it, so be grateful
for everything I do for you.
I guess it… must have been hard for you.
- [phone buzzing]
- Hey, Ho-jae.
[music fades]
UNKNOWN NUMBER
Yep, hello?
Um, hello?
[Chae-ok] It's me.
Where are you?
How's your injury? Are you all right?
Can I come in for a minute?
What…
[pensive music playing]
What are you doing here?
Does your offer…
still stand?
To partner with each other.
I wanna work with you.
[reverential music playing]
[reverential music continues]
[phone buzzes]
- Yes, hello?
- [music fades]
[chiming]
["Dawn" by Kim A Reum playing]
♪ Walking down the road ♪
♪ Where the darkness falls ♪
♪ I see the truth ♪
♪ That lead us through the ebb and tide ♪
♪ Our souls will blend ♪
♪ Love that never fades
And never cease ♪
♪ All right, all right, all right ♪
♪ In your embrace ♪
♪ I could never feel the pain ♪
♪ I could even let go of all fears ♪
♪ Your eyes shine like guiding lights ♪
♪ In this tough world ♪
♪ Our stories unfold ♪
♪ All the traces will never disappear ♪
♪ In your eyes I see the dawn ♪
♪ When all the hope seems lost ♪
♪ Your love gives me strength ♪
♪ With you by my side ♪
♪ All my fears just fade away ♪
♪ Shadows loomed over, don't be afraid ♪
♪ Our story lives on in the city's lore ♪
♪ In the heart of Seoul ♪
♪ Oh in this urban canvas ♪
♪ Like stars we will shine bright ♪
♪ Finding the place that we both belong ♪
♪ Follow me through the dark ♪
♪ Oh in this city's chaos ♪
♪ We're lighting up the skies ♪
♪ Keep searching for answers
To who we are ♪
♪ Till the end of the time ♪
♪ Go on ♪
♪ On, on ♪
♪ Follow me through the dark ♪
♪ Go on ♪
♪ On, on ♪
♪ Love will grow in the symphony of life ♪
♪ I'm in the deep end ♪
♪ Veiled in the fog ♪
[music fades]